

Ju-I Kuo
FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Ambitious front-end developer with 8 years of work experiences in international projects and 1.5 year experiences in web development and UX design.

Quick learner, goal oriented, curious and problem solving person looking for new challenges.

LANGUAGE

Mandarin English

Swedish French



CONTACT INFORMATION

Helsingborg, Sweden

+46-765011688

✓ rubitiara@gmail.com

https://github.com/rubikuo

in www.linkedin.com/in/rubikuo

Новву







Travel Photography

Yoga

EDUCATION

2019 - 2021.06 Front-End Development

EC Utbildning, Helsingborg

Enhancing in JavaScript by focusing on React.js, testing, UX design,

Back-End developement.

2019 Front-End Development

Komvux, Helsingborg

6 month intensive course in HTML,

CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap,

Jquery, Angular, API, GitHub, CLI,

Scrum, FireBase.

2005 - 2009 B.A. Radio, Television and Film

Shih Hsin Univerisity, Taipei Taiwan

GPA 3.9 (av 4)

PROJECTS

MyTrello React, Passport.js, Node.js, MongoDB

https://mytrellos.herokuapp.com/

CloudyBox React, JS, Oauth, Dropbox API

https://cloudybox.surge.sh/

iQuiz JS, React, UX, WAI-ARIA

http://rubis-iquiz.surge.sh/

Wifi Points Finder

Hbg API, Firebase, jQuery, Angular

https://hbg-wifi-finder.surge.sh/

Competencies

HTML	React.js	Scrum	Team Work
CSS/SASS	Angular	Photoshop	Koordinering
jQuery	Node.js	Adobe XD	Kommunikation
JavaScript	MongoDB	Illustrator	Kundtjänst

WORK EXPRERIENCE

International Sales 2009-2017

- Customer Relationship Management (CRM)
- Worked with external customer service and internal departments to ensure every commercial project reached its goal and was completed according to plan.
- Managed social media marketing.

See appendix for more details.

<< Annex >>

Ju-I Kuo FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Awards / Activity

Last Mile Hack

DAPP - Delivery App 2019 Helsingborg, Sverige

Taiwan Women's Hockey

Women's AHF Cup Coordinator, Tour Leader 2016 Bangkok, Thailand

Shih Hsin Delegation Member

International academic exchange 2009 Beijing, China 2008 Boston, Missouri, Michigan, U.S.A.

Additional Course

2019 - 2020 SAS

Hermods Helsingborg

2018 SFI

Folkuniversitetet, Helsingborg

2013 - 2014

French

I.F.C.A.D. Brussels, Belgium

VOLUNTEER

2010 Taiwan International Documentary Festival English Host

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 International Operations Coordinator
Orien Trading Corp., Taiwan

Coordinated triangular trading processes and maintained supplier and customer relationships with the help of strong communication and coordination skills.

2015 -2017 International Operations Coordinator
Damei Travel Service Co. Ltd, Taiwan

Reduced costs by 10-15% for each group trip by renegotiating hotel and event contracts in line with company policy, financing and terms.

2013-2014 PR & Marketing Coordinator
Dechamps-Presse SPRL, Brussels, Belgium

Maintained and managed social media, advertising and marketing tactics, to achieve exposure goals to public.

2012-2013 International Sales Coordinator

Taiwan Nanotechnology Corp., Taiwan

Worked with external customer service and internal organizational companies to ensure that each of the commercial projects met the objectives and was completed according to plan.

2009-2015 Freelance Communication Coordinator

Provided communication and coordination services at international exhibitions and activities throughout Asia:

2015 KBC Fair Shanghai, China
2015 Timtos Fair Taipei, Taiwan
2012 Gifts and Premium Fair, Hong Kong
2012 Beabi Company, Manila, Philippines
2011 Marlboro Footwear Ltd, Dongquan, China

2009-2011 International Sales Coordinator
Trade Way Company, Taiwan

Increased customer base by 10% in one year.